

Contact

Phone

+49 (0)1577 350 52 <u>02</u>

Email

merayo.rafa@gmail.com

Address

Frankfurt am Main. Willing to relocate

Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/rafaelmerayo/

Github

https://github.com/RafaMR

Expertise

FRONT END CODING

- JavaScript (ES6), React
- HTML & CSS

BACK END CODING

- NodeJS & Express
- Mongo DB

Languages

Spanish - Native

English - Full profesional proficiency

German - Full profesional proficiency

Rafael Merayo

Full Stack Developer with a background in Sales

Full Stack Developer with a background in Sales and several years of experience at online tech companies looking forward to changing careers and joining a project to put into practice my technical skills and work experience acquired.

Experience

O January 2022 - August 2022

Student. Web development Bootcamp. Ironhack.

- Six months part-time immersive course to become a Full Stack Developer.
- Learned Front-end design and Back-end architecture fundamentals, using top-notch technologies such as JavaScript, React, HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, NodeJs, ExpressJs, MongoDb, Axios, Git and Github.
- Developed a total of three projects including:

IRONPUMP (AGITHUB)

- Full-Stack app to upload and manage your own workouts.
- Built in JavaScript using React.js, SASS, MongoDB, REST-API and Axios.
- Deployed on Netlify and Heroku.

MEETECH (AGITHUB)

- Networking app to upload and look for tech events.
- Built with Handlebars and JavaScript using Express, Node.js, Cloudinary and MongoDB.
- Deployed on Netlify and Heroku.

VIDEO GAME ELON MARS (>GITHUB)

- Positioned this video game on Product Hunt as the 5th product of the day on 18/04/2022.
- Object-oriented programming using plain JavaScript and canvas.
- Deployed on Netlify.

November 2015 - January 2023

Sales Manager Spain. eGENTIC. Frankfrut am Main.

- eGENTIC is the world leader in online lead generation offering companies qualified consumer leads generated through Online Sweepstakes and Email Marketing.
- Responsible for the new business acquisition and account management of top-tier clients in the Spanish market.
- Helped to position Spain as the second top market in EMEA by increasing the annual team revenue on average by +9,3% and overachieving on average +35% of personal annual sales goals of 720k€/year. Team yearly revenue exceeding € 4 million.

March 2012 - October 2015

Sales Manager Spain Whisbi. (Google contractor). Barcelona

- Whisbi worked on behalf of Google in Spain helping digital marketing agencies to acquire new business on AdWords (Google Partners Program).
- Responsible for a portfolio of 50 to 60 agencies contributing to an +7,8% increase in AdWords average investment and + € 1.35 million yearly revenue.

Education

October 2006 - March 2009

Diplomatura Turismo. BA in Hospitality management.

Universidad Autónoma de Madrid. University degree. 180 ECTS.